<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on The Church of GNU</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on The Church of GNU</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 13:21:29 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://info.antisoftware.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Selfhosting</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/selfhosting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/selfhosting/</guid><description>Self hosting resources # Learning resources # LandChad: A site dedicated to turning internet peasants into Internet Landlords by showing them how to setup websites, email servers, chat servers and everything in between. vagrant-vmware-box: How to create VMware vagrant box roll.urown.net: How to roll your own private self-hosted internet services The Cyber Plumber&amp;rsquo;s Handbook: The definitive guide to Secure Shell (SSH) tunneling, port redirection, and bending traffic like a boss.</description></item><item><title>Fix ArchWiki's awful styling</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/posts/archwiki_styling/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 21:02:26 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/posts/archwiki_styling/</guid><description>By @x86asm_
Full fix (JS)
const key = &amp;#39;useskinversion&amp;#39;; const params = new URLSearchParams(window.location.search); const version = params.get(key); if (!version) { // replace makes redirect not reflected in the browser back history window.location.replace(`${window.location.href}?${key}=1`); } Size fix (CSS)
.skin--responsive, .mw-page-container, .mw-content-container, .mw-workspace-container, .mw-article-toolbar-container { max-width: none; margin-left: 0; margin-right: 0; }</description></item><item><title>Setup printing in Arch for HP Printers (USB)</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/posts/hp_printing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 20:54:52 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/posts/hp_printing/</guid><description>from @iceman
Learn how to setup printing services on Arch Linux for HP based printers connected via USB
This is mostly for hplip dependent printers, usually there&amp;rsquo;s a package for your printer either on aur or the official repositories. Check the wiki before you follow this guide. The content was written well over 2 years ago, as a more of a &amp;ldquo;note&amp;rdquo; rather than being a &amp;ldquo;tutorial/guide&amp;rdquo;.
Connect your printer Installing CUPS and other required stuff $ pacman -S cups $ systemctl enable cups $ systemctl start cups $ pacman -S hplip $ hp-setup -i Follow steps and download plugin and it should work.</description></item><item><title>Compilers</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/compilers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/compilers/</guid><description>Compilers # Resources # acwj: A Compiler Writing Journey [GitHub] Low-Level Software Security for Compiler Developers: [GitHub] [Book] Compiler Infographics: [Link] Cornell CS6120: Advanced compilers course, taught at Cornell LLVM # 2019 LLVM Developers’ Meeting: A. Warzynski “Writing an LLVM Pass: 101”: [YouTube] Writing LLVM passes Out-of-tree LLVM passes in Rust: [GitHub] A collection of out-of-tree LLVM passes for teaching and learning: [GitHub] Learn LLVM 12: [GitHub] Kaleidoscope: Implementing a language with LLVM: [C++] [Rust] inkwell: It&amp;rsquo;s a new kind of wrapper for exposing LLVM safely Tools # Godbolt: Compiler explorer [Link] Dogbolt: Dogbolt is an interactive online decompiler which shows equivalent C-like output of decompiled programs from many popular decompilers.</description></item><item><title>Computer Architecture and Hardware</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/hardware/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/hardware/</guid><description> Computer Architecture and Hardware # Computer Architecture # cpu-internals: Intel / AMD CPU Internals [GitHub] Digital Design and Computer Architecture by Onur Mutlu @ ETH Zurich: Onur Mutlu&amp;rsquo;s livestream lecture videos from the freshman-level Digital Design and Computer Architecture course taught at ETH Zürich in Spring 2021 [YouTube] [Course page] nand2tetris: Building a Modern Computer From First Principles [Link] Field Programmable Gate Arrays (FPGA) resources Build your own FPGA: [Link] FPGA architecture overview: [Link] Trusted Computing # Introduction To Trusted Computing by Ariel Segall@OpenSecurityTraining: [YouTube] [Homepage] DRM internals: How Netflix/Amazon DRM ACTUALLY works [Reddit] Device drivers # Tools # pc-keyboard: PS/2 Keyboard Decoder in Rust Libraries # winapi-kmd-rs: Windows Kernel-Mode Drivers written in Rust kmd-env-rs: Rust environment for the Windows Kernel-Mode Drivers pawn: Extract BIOS firmware from Intel-based workstations and laptops</description></item><item><title>Computer Graphics</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/graphics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/graphics/</guid><description> Computer Graphics # Learning resources # Computer Graphics from ScratchLink Framebuffers # Programming the Linux Framebuffer: [Link] Back to the Linux Framebuffer! Linux Framebuffer support in free software: [YouTube] Scratch A Pixel: A free educational site that progressively introduces you to the world of computer graphics: [Link] Learning Modern 3D Graphics Programming: [Link] Shaders # The Book of Shaders: This is a gentle step-by-step guide through the abstract and complex universe of Fragment Shaders [Link] OpenGL # Learn OpenGL: Link OpenGL Wiki: Link Vulkan # Vulkan Tutorial: Link Tools # Framebuffer viewer: fbv (FrameBuffer Viewer) is a simple program to view pictures on a Linux framebuffer device [GitHub]</description></item><item><title>Concurrency</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/concurrency/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/concurrency/</guid><description> Concurrency # Resources # IIT Delhi COL 869: Special Topics in Concurrency</description></item><item><title>Cryptography</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/cryptography/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/cryptography/</guid><description> Cryptography # Learning resources # Serious Cryptography: A Practical Introduction to Modern Encryption by Jean-Philippe Aumasson [Link] Tools # Keyoxide: Decentralized identity verification [Link]</description></item><item><title>Distributed Systems</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/distributed_systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/distributed_systems/</guid><description> Distributed Systems # Resources # Distributed Systems (3rd edition): [Link]</description></item><item><title>Emulation</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/emulation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/emulation/</guid><description>Emulation # Architecture # Chip-8 # Chip-8 Research Facility Creating a CHIP-8 interpreter/emulator in C++14 - Bisqwit How to write a basic CHIP-8 interpreter Timendus&amp;rsquo;s Chip-8 Test Suite Writing a CHIP-8 emulator CHIP-8 Technical Reference Nintendo Entertainment System (NES) # See 65xx family resources 6502 instruction set reference The NesDev wiki NES emulator development guide Overview of writing a NES emulator Articles on writing a NES emulator, among other things Sample ROMs Nintendo 64 (N64) # See MIPs resources N64 Docs N64 Brew Info About N64 Boot Code Sony PlayStation 1 (PSX) # See MIPs resoruces Guide to writing a PSX emulator PSX GPU texture pipeline PSX OSS BIOS Tools # retroarch: RetroArch is a frontend for emulators, game engines and media players.</description></item><item><title>Gaming stuff</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/gaming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/gaming/</guid><description> Gaming # Game security # awesome-game-security: [GitHub] Game Hacking Academy: [Link] The Ultimate Game Hacking Resource: [GitHub] Game Hacking playlist: [Link] Anti Cheat Systems # Valve Anti Cheat(VAC): [Link] Battleye: [Link] Easy Anti-Cheat: [Link] Vanguard: [Link] Research Papers and Conferences # GameSec Conference: [Link] TZMon: Improving mobile game security with ARM trustzone: [Link] Books # Game Hacking: Developing autonomous bots for online games by Nick Cano [Link]</description></item><item><title>Mathematics</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/mathematics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/mathematics/</guid><description> Mathematics # Learning resources # Learn Mathematics from START to FINISH: [YouTube] An Interactive Way to Learn Linear Algebra: Link Paul&amp;rsquo;s Notes: [Link] Online communities # LessWrong: LessWrong is an online forum and community dedicated to improving human reasoning and decision-making. We seek to hold true beliefs and to be effective at accomplishing our goals. Each day, we aim to be less wrong about the world than the day before [Link]</description></item><item><title>Miscellaneous</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/miscellaneous/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/miscellaneous/</guid><description>Miscellaneous # Audio Engineering # Let There Be Sound RED interview guide: This site was written as a guide for potential users to learn about music formats, transcodes, torrenting, and burning and ripping Orpheus interview guide: This site was written as a guide for potential users to learn about music formats, transcodes, torrenting, and burning and ripping. Introduction to HiFi: This site is intended to educate music listeners on a broad range of topics related to improving the listening experience Databases # Cstack Database Tutorial Note-taking # How I&amp;rsquo;m able to take notes in mathematics lectures using LaTeX and Vim Latex input for impatient scholars Org-Mode awesome-neovim: Collections of awesome neovim plugins More learning resources # The Book Of Secret Knowledge: A collection of inspiring lists, manuals, cheatsheets, blogs, hacks, one-liners, cli/web tools and more.</description></item><item><title>Networking</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/networks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/networks/</guid><description>Networking # Computer Networks # Resources # CompTIA A+ Certification Video Course: By PowerCert Animated Videos [YouTube] BGP Internet Exchange Points (IXP): A Primer on Internet Exchange Points for Policymakers and Non-Engineers [Paper] Tools # Reverse proxy: caddy: ast and extensible multi-platform HTTP/1-2-3 web server with automatic HTTPS Scalable overlay networks: These can be used to punch through the NAT without all the mess that port forwarding and dynamic IP addressing involves Tailscale: Tailscale is a WireGuard-based app that makes secure, private networks easy for teams of any scale [Link] ZeroTierOne: A smart Ethernet switch for Earth [GitHub] headscale: An open source, self-hosted implementation of the Tailscale control server [GitHub] netmaker: Netmaker makes networks with WireGuard.</description></item><item><title>Online privacy and digital security</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/privacy/</guid><description>Online privacy and digital security # Privacy guides # The Hitchhiker’s Guide to Online Anonymity: How I learned to start worrying and love privacy anonymity [Link] PrivacyGuides: Massive organizations are monitoring your online activities. Privacy Guides is your central privacy and security resource to protect yourself online [Link] Data Collection Techniques: How third party tracking and data mining is accomplished [Link] EFF Surveillance Self Defence: Tips, Tools and How-tos for Safer Online Communications by EFF [Link] switching.</description></item><item><title>Operating systems</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/operating_systems/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/operating_systems/</guid><description>Operating systems # Theoretical concepts # Hack The Kernel: ops-class.org includes everything you need to learn about operating systems online [Link] Understanding Virtual Memory: Virtual Memory lecture for Introduction to Computer Architecture at Uppsala University [YouTube] osdev Wiki: This website provides information about the creation of operating systems and serves as a community for those people interested in OS development [Link] Writing an OS in Rust: [Link] DECS: Design and Engineering of Computer Systems taught at IIT Bombay [Link] OSTEP: Operating Systems: Three Easy Pieces [Link] Operating System Concepts (10th edition): [Link] CS-6210-Advanced-Operating-Systems-Notes: Notes for GaTech&amp;rsquo;s Advanced Operating Systems course (CS6210) os_kernel_lab: OS kernel labs based on Rust/C Lang &amp;amp; RISC-V 64/X86-32 Linux # Learning resources # linux-insides: A book-in-progress about the linux kernel and its insides [Book] [GitHub] The Executable and Linkable Format (ELF) by Intezer Labs Part 1 Section and Segments Part 2 Symbols Part 3 Relocations Part 4 Dynamic Linking Understanding the memory layout of Linux executables: [GitHub Gist] awesome-elf Tools # quBSD: A FreeBSD jails and bhyve wrapper; which emulates a Qubes-like containerization schema [GitHub] explainshell: match command-line arguments to their help text [Link] WSL-Hello-sudo: Let&amp;rsquo;s sudo by face recognition of Windows Hello on Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL).</description></item><item><title>Piracy</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/piracy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/piracy/</guid><description>Piracy # Guides # FreeMediaHeckYeah: The Largest Collection of Free Stuff On The Internet! AnimePiracy Piracy Index: This website is a collection of the best digital piracy resources. This will help you get started on your pirate voyage TheWiki: Welcome to the wiki for all things related to anime and more, ranging from easy to digest tutorials to full blown guides! Champagne Piracy Wiki r/piracy Megathread Ripped Guide GentooMen Library Esoteria Avenue CaptainRookie: Digital audio guides and tutorials covering MP3 and FLAC ripping, editing, converting and organising your digital music collection Encoding guides Archived Things AHD&amp;rsquo;s encoding guide A Guide to x264: Dropbox PDF link Miscellaneous # Warez: The Infrastructure and Aesthetics of Piracy: Understanding the pirate ecosystem Understanding pirate multimedia releases: Understanding x264, x265, codecs and stuff Reddit IMAs I run a &amp;ldquo;topsite&amp;rdquo; FTP server and I&amp;rsquo;m in the piracy scene.</description></item><item><title>Programming concepts</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/programming/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/programming/</guid><description>Programming resources # Programming language theory # Programming Concepts: Taught at UIC by John Bell, this web site contains course notes for general concepts in computer programming, independent of any particular language or implementation. Some sections contain links to language-specific implementation notes [Course] Elements of programming: Decomposing programs into a system of algorithmic components [Link] hacker-laws: Laws, Theories, Principles and Patterns that developers will find useful Assembly # Learning resources # assemblyShenanigans: My attempt to teach others about microprocessors and programming in IA-32 and IA-64 assembly, and to spread the word of how awesome it is assemblyTutorials: This project was put together to teach myself NASM x86 assembly language on Linux optimization-manual: Contains the source code examples described in the &amp;ldquo;Intel® 64 and IA-32 Architectures Optimization Reference Manual&amp;rdquo; asmdb: Instructions database and utilities for X86/X64 and ARM (THUMB/A32/A64) architectures Assemblers Almanac: List of resources compiled from the Assembler&amp;rsquo;s Community server [GitLab] OpenSecurityTraining Intel x86: [Link] Instruction set reference Intel® 64 and IA-32 Instruction Set Reference [Link] X86 Opcode and Instruction Reference [Link] Programmed Introduction to MIPS Assembly Language: Interactive first course in assembly language programming using the MIPS32 processor and the SPIM simulator [Link] asmtutor: NASM Assembly Language Tutorials [Link] Linux system call table for X86-64: [Link] Learn x86-64 using Windows: [Link] How to Learn x86 by Uni Of Virginia: [Link] Tools # rappel: A linux-based assembly REPL for x86, amd64, armv7, and armv8 ia32-doc: IA32-doc is a project which aims to put as many definitions from the Intel Manual into machine-processable format as possible C # Learning resources # Learn C [Link] Learn by doing # Write a Shell in C by Stephen Brennan: [Link] Libraries and stuff # STB: Single File Public Domain Libraries [GitHub] C++ # Learning resources # CPPreference: The place to be if you need to look something up about C or C++ [Link] LearnCPP: A good and extensive tutorial covering a lot of C++ features in a comprehensible way [Link] The Definitive C++ Book Guide and List: StackOverflow CppCon: All Cppcon talks [YouTube] CppCon 2018: Matt Godbolt “The Bits Between the Bits: How We Get to main()&amp;quot;: [YouTube] Libraries and stuff # json: Modern C++ JSON library: [GitHub] Boost: Modern C++ library with lots of submodules useful for various stuff: [GitHub] Go # Learning resources # Effective Go: [Link] Tour Golang: [Link] GoLang Wiki: [Github] GoBooks: List of Golang books Ruby # Learning resources # Ruby By Example: [Link] Python # Learning Resources # Dive Into Python: [Link] awesome-python-books: Directory of Python books LISP # Learning Resources # Lisp Course: [Link] Rust # Learning resources # rustlings: Small exercises to get you used to reading and writing Rust code!</description></item><item><title>Security research</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/security_research/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/security_research/</guid><description>Security research # Learning Resource # Proof of Concept or GTFO mirror by Ange Albertini: [Link] [GitHub] How the Best Hackers Learn Their Craft: [YouTube] Open Security Training: [Link] Awesome-Hacking: A collection of various awesome lists for hackers, pentesters and security researchers wargame-nexus: A sorted and updated list of security wargame sites 1earn: The security knowledge framework maintained by the fffffff0x team includes content that is not limited to web security, industrial control security, forensics, emergency response, blue team facility deployment, post-infiltration, Linux security, and various target drone writeups AppSecEzine: AppSec Ezine Public repository Reverse engineering # Tools # awesome-reverse-engineering: Reverse Engineering Resources About All Platforms(Windows/Linux/macOS/Android/iOS/IoT) And Every Aspect!</description></item><item><title>Virtualization</title><link>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/virtualization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://info.antisoftware.net/docs/learning-resources/virtualization/</guid><description>Virtualization # Resources # IITB CS695: Virtualization and Cloud Computing by Mythili Vutukuru [Link] Quick QEMU-VMs via CLI: [Link] awesome-virtualization: Collection of resources about virtualization Hyper-101-In-Rust: The materials of &amp;ldquo;Hypervisor 101 in Rust&amp;rdquo;, a one-day long course, to quickly learn hardware-assisted virtualization technology and its application for high-performance fuzzing on Intel/AMD processors Tools # Quickemu: Quickly create and run optimised Windows, macOS and Linux desktop virtual machines OSX-KVM: Run macOS on QEMU/KVM.</description></item></channel></rss>